NABEEL AHMED KHAN

FULL STACK ENGINEER

PROFILE SUMMARY

I am a Full Stack Engineer with a passion for design. I have experience working with Angular, React, React Native, Node.js, NestJS, Express and other web frameworks, libraries and tools. I have a keen eye for responsive web design, and I spend most of my time working with Web and Mobile Apps.

CONTACT DETAILS

92 333 033 0889 nabeelahmedkhan.tk nabeel-a-khan@outlook.com linkedin.com/in/nabeel-a-khan github.com/n4beel Karachi. Sindh

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

 Runner-up of Procom 2019 Web Design and Development Competition

TECH SKILLS

Responsive Web User Interface Design and Development, Graphic Design, HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, jQuery, D3, Bootstrap, Angular, React, Redux, React Native, Node.js, Express, NestJS

PROJECTS

- crypto-kar.web.app
- parho-parhao.web.app
- foodies-web.web.app
- chat-appweb.web.app
- asan-compiler.web.app
- barter-webapp.web.app
- · tic-tic-tic.web.app
- ganexus-ui.web.app

WORK EXPERIENCE

Lead MERN Stack Engineer

Xehen.ai (Xord.one) | May 2020 - Present

 My responsibilities include managing and working with a team of Full Stack Engineers, we develop web and mobile applications using cutting edge methods and technologies

Front End Developer

Edgeon Solutions | June 2019 - May 2020

- Developed multiple Primary Projects regarding fleet management, labor management and auto financing with support for multiple languages and orientations using Angular 8.
- Designed and developed company's portfolio website.

UI/UX Developer

Universal Information System | Nov 2018 - May 2019

- Designed and developed multiple components of company's flagship fleet management project.
- · Designed and developed company's portfolio

EDUCATION

University of Karachi (UBIT)

BSSE (Final Year) | 2017 - Present

Government Dehli College

Intermediate | 2014 - 2016

Sagib Public School

Matriculation | 2012 - 2014